{
    "id": "d6db5fe3475b4b3dad7c111ee9a64e5a",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ............................................ a prize for standing first in the quiz competition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "win",
                "has win"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ........................................... my instructions?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carry out",
                "carried out",
                "carries out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................... since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "am waiting",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The box was so heavy that the boy ....................................... lift it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot",
                "could not",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When I saw the child, he .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cries",
                "was crying",
                "has cried"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................ to my native place a week ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We got our roof ............................................ before the rainy season set in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repair",
                "repaired",
                "repairing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Not one of them dreamt of doing what he never ......................................... to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "attempts",
                "attempted",
                "has attempted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She .............................................. the railway station before the train came.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reach",
                "reached",
                "had reached"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................ school last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "have left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}